

Olivier Daigneault
3D Creator



https://olivier-daigneault. netlify.app/accueil









Curriculum Vitae

My career goal is to specialize in the modeling of 3D environments and objects, as well as 3D animation.

I'm very versatile in the multimedia field, from Web development to video editing. I enjoy taking on new challenges to improve my knowledge.

Skills

3D Modeling

- Object and character modeling
- 3D Animation
- 3D Texturing

Web Development

- Graphic design
- Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Website hosting

Games Development

- Video game programming
- Creation of particle systems
- Game design

Design

- Intuitive user interface
- Improving ergonomics
- Creating attractive experiences

Qualities

- Autonomous
- Versatile
- Hard-working
- Team player

Hobbies

- · Video games
- Reading & movies
- 3D modeling and printing
- Cats

Software





















Programming languages











Olivier Daigneault
3D Creator



https://olivier-daigneault. netlify.app/accueil









School projects

2D video game project

- Develop the visual style of the game (environment, Tilemap & objects)
- Create and animate characters for integration into Unity
- Produce particle systems for 2D visuals (Unity)

3D video game project

- Create 3D characters and objects (Blender)
- Create static and animated textures (Substance 3D Designer)
- Produce particle systems for 3D visuals (Unity)

Education

Multimedia integration techniques Cégep de Saint-Jérôme (2019 - 2024)

Science, computing and mathematics
Collège Lionel-Groulx (2017 - 2019)

Work experience

01 Studio

Level Designer

(full time)

May 2024 - Present

- In-game map creation for gamemodes and assets pack showcase
- 3D assets creation with the visual style of the game and blender plugin

Pemana

Versatile Web Developer

(10 weeks internship)

June 2023 - August 2023

- Develop multiple websites (Vue3 HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Host sites with a domain name on GitHub Pages
- Produce graphic elements (images & logos)

Casteliers

Communications Assistant

(30 weeks contract)

Sept. 2022 - May 2023

- Manage WordPress websites
- Produce graphics elements and videos editing
- Manage social media and newsletter

Atmosphäre

Marketing Assistant

(10 weeks internship)

June 2022 - August 2022

- 3D animation (3ds Max)
- Create communication tools
- Translate documents